in fact you treat me badly too you treat me
по факту ко мне вы тоже плохо относитесь
yes yes well and I do nothing well how do you
относитесь да да ну а я ничего не делаю
treat me that way that you
ну как вы вот том-то и относимся что вы
do nothing
ничего не делаете
hello hello I am from the city of
здравствуйте здравствуйте я из города
Khmelnitsky you are from Russia
Хмельницкий вы из России
where is Western Siberia who is Omsk
откуда западной Сибири кто омск
Tyumen Tyumen
тюмень тюмень
damn I thought it was not Western
блин думал это не западная
what are you talking about today
о чём общаетесь сегодня
I just sewed up well
я только зашвал
and what do you want to talk about do you
ну а о чём хотите поговорить у вас же
have any preferences
есть какие-то предпочтения
yes no just to while away the time while
дабо-то нет просто скоротать время пока
my phone is resetting
мой телефон обнуляется
and what happened to the phone
а что с телефоном случилось
nothing they gave me a watch and I need to update
ничего подарили часы и нужно обновить
iOS it's
iOS
cool what do you do
прикольно кем работаете
in the morgue pathologist
в морге патологанатом
no and who is a forensic expert no that's very
нет а кто суд эксперт нет это очень
tough well and who is a
жёстко ну а кем
tathopractor who prepares people
татопрактик который подготавливает людей
for farewell
к прощанию
that is there to wash them dress them that and
то есть там помыть их одеть вот это да
put on makeup yes I understand and
накрасить да понял
what do you do
а вы чем занимаетесь
you do I am a pathologist this is
вы чем занимаетесь я патологанатом это
not a joke how so therefore
не шутка
so when you
как поэтому поэтому поэтому когда вы
said that in the morgue I am like that I think
сказали что в морге я такой так думаю
this is some kind of joke or something I think you are not alike
это какой-то прикол что ли думаю вы не
we have girls who
похожи у нас как бы девушки есть которые
work  yes but they
работают да но они как-то немножко не
look a little different from you
так выглядят как вы
I suddenly
я неожиданно
and you have a morgue like at what kind of
а у вас морг типа при какой там при
city hospital regional what kind of
городской больнице областной какой при
Well we have one morgue for Tyumen one morgue
Ну у нас один морг на Тюмень один морг
yes and how many people are in Tyumen
да а сколько в Тюмении населения
890,000
890.000
well one morgue or is it just
да ну один морк или он просто
One morgue and recently built well opened the
Один морг и недавно построили ну открыли
first crematorium crematorium yes I understand
первый крематорий крематорий да понял
because well for 800,000 there
потому что ну на 800.000 уже по-любому
should be crematoriums there anyway well of
должна быть там крематории
course they did it beautifully but
ну там конечно красиво сделали но
that used to be more morgues I don't know
это раньше было больше моргов не знаю
why it happened but apparently everyone
почему так случилось но видимо все все
wants to live there are fewer there have been
хотят жить стало меньше сократились э
fewer people the thing is that you
людей стало меньше дело в том что
understand well
понимаете
no it's been gone for a long time that is still even well
ну нет его давно уже нету то есть ещё
if we analyze yes the topic so to
даже ну если мы разберём да тему так
speak military and covid before all these
скажем военную и ковида до ещё всех этих
moments well there are fewer people the population of
моментов ну людей меньше население
Russia is decreasing decreasing all the more so
России уменьшается уменьшается тем более
many people left Tyumen then they
э из Тюмении уезжали многие это потом
started coming from Asian countries from the
там начали с стран Азии приезжать из
Caucasus well in
Кавказа
general listen but here's a practical
ну вообще а слушайте а вот практический
question yes I'm a pathologist yes I'm in
да вопрос я как патологонатом да я в
my field  I understand but I'm
своей сфере разбираюсь а вот мне
interested in your point of view yes as a
интересно вашу точку зрения да как
person who, let's say, prepares the
человека который э готовит скажем
deceased for the
усопшего к ээ
rituals so that, let's say, they can presentably
обрядам чтобы скажем так презентабельно
hand him over to his relatives yes what do
отдать его родственникам да
you think you would
как вы считаете во что бы вы вот
dress Putin in
нарядили Путина
[music]
[музыка]
those who will taste the copper ones, those four
те кто будет пробовать медные те четверо
chefs who will leave based on the results of the tasting,
кулинаров которые по итогам дегустации
which of the participants will make it through to the finals and who
кто из участников пройдёт финал а кто
will go home well you understand that this is a
отправится домой ну ты понимаешь что это
provocation yes this is a provocative question
провокация да это провокационный вопрос
I, as a pathologist, understand what I would
я как патологонатом я понимаю что я бы с
do with him yes I'm interested as you
ним сделал да мне интересно как вот вы
see what he will be in he is the president of the same
видите в чём его будут это же президент
country yes how should they dress him
такой же страны да как его должны одеть
in front of him anyway
перед он же всё равно уже старенький
he will be old soon well we will all be there well he will soon be
скоро он
all under God we walk no one knows
все под Богом ходим никто неизвестно
when he will die well what do you think he should be
когда умрёт ну как вы считаете во что
dressed in I do
его нужно одеть
n't think we need to keep this
а я не считаю нужно поддерживать эту
topic of conversation I think he
тему для разговора я считаю что его
should be in short without any burial well
нужно короче без всякого погребение ну
if he wants a crematorium then I mean
если он захочет крематорий то в смысле
he wants it in short
он захочет этого нужно короче
this and everything straight without
реально да вот этот и всё прямо без
any farewells without
всяких прощаний без
anything do you really want that  such
ничего вы реально хотите чтобы такого
with some other processions they buried a
ещё с какими-то процессиями хоронили
bag of
мешочек
softness a bag for the future you don't
смядкость мешочек на будущее вы не
work in a morgue
работаете в морге
why and because you say a person
почему а потому что вы скажем человек
who works in a morgue yes with us or
который работает в морге да у нас или
they treat such questions very simply
они очень просто относятся к таким
with jokes mod yes for you it's wild
вопросам с шутками мо да для вас дико
for you it's clear that you haven't
для вас дико видно что вы не
encountered
сталкивались с
this or you've been working recently
этим либо либо работаете недавно
I'll say so that I adore all the
я скажу так что я обожаю всю
ritual in general that is connected with the morgue
ритуальную вообще вот связанную с моргом
with all the farewells I love the cemetery I love
со всеми прощаниями кладбище люблю люблю
farewell ceremonies I love in general in any
церемонии прощания люблю вообще в любом
sense but I'll say so that
смысле но скажу так что а своего
I would preserve my president of my country with
президента своей страны я похранила бы
dignity as it should be make-up
достойно как положено грим
flowers attributes all
цветы атрибутика вся
that is to me in general listen but
то есть мне вообще слушайте а вот
look in ancient Egypt there was such a
смотрите в Древнем Египте был такой
custom let's say when this
скажем обычай когда этот
pharaoh died yes with him everything he was
фараон погибал да с ним все его короче
buried with him don't
его погребали вместе с ним не хотите ли
you want to go with your king yes when he
вы вот вместе со своим царём да когда он
moves his horses too since you love him so much
двинет кони тоже пойти раз вы его так
that you prepare to kiss him don't
любите что готовимцу целовать да не
you want to go to the tomb with him
хотите ли вы в гробницу вместе с ним
so that even in the next world you can kiss him
пойти чтобы аж на том свете целовать ему
too
тоже
but can the question be no
а можно вопрос нельзя
sorry but  I will ask him
жаль но я его
why with the flag of Ukraine with this coat of arms or
почему с флагом Украины с вот гербом или
whatever you have and on the T-shirt you
что это у вас а на футболке вы
speak in the Russian
разговариваете на максимально русском
language as much as possible yes because you are Russians
языке да потому что вы россияне
so much that you do not understand the
настолько ту Да что не понимаете
Ukrainian language therefore in order to
украинский язык поэтому для того чтобы
convey all our misfortune and contempt for
донести всю нашу ненасть и презрение к
you we speak this in the only
вам мы это говорим на единственно
language you understand in Russian with you can
понятном вам языке на русском с
withstand the killing of people in Ukraine
вытодержите убийство людей в Украине
yes glory to Russia
да слава России
together with the president
вместе с президентом
that's how you need to talk to all these
вот так нужно говорить с этими всеми
Russian leopards yes they go out to
леопардами русскими да они выходят в
chat roulette smiling yes I went out to talk
чат-рулеточку улыбаются да я вышла
iPhone watch chose Ukraine
поговорить часики iPhone выбрала Украину
yes so that they catch our
да для того что они отлавливают наших
soldiers here they catch ours there
солдатиков тут они отлавливают наших там
lei and talk about detached topics yes
лей и говорят на отстранённые темы да
so that we are ordinary people and then
для того чтобы мы ж простые люди а потом
glory to Russia no we are the president and so
слава России нет мы президент и так
on
дальше
yes put a plus who wants to
да поставьте плюсик кто хочет
see Putin as soon as possible
побыстрее видеть
even in Trump's arms yes
Путина пусть даже в объятиях Трампа да
together in the crematorium
вместе в крематории
like a subpost comment
лайк подпоска комент
about a priest heart
о попик сердечко вам
thank you
спасибо
let's chat my name is Andrey
давайте пообщаемся меня зовут Андрей
I know who you are and what is your name
я знаю кто вы а вас как зовут
Lena Elena  What city are you from the
лена елена вы из какого
capital city of Smolensk Smolensk I
града стольный град Смоленск смоленск
know Belarus yes formerly occupied by
знаю беларусь да бывшая оккупированная
Russia
Россией
no not occupied that's me 43 years old and
нет не оккупирована это мне 43 года а
you barely how much and
вам еле на сколько
how much will you give well even interesting m with
а сколько дадите ну даже интересно м с
confiscation or without
конфискацией или без
what does it mean with confiscation well the
что значит с конфискации ну их там
prosecutor gives them 10 years there with confiscation of
прокурор даёт там 10 лет с конфискации
property
имущества
understandable
понятно
okay oh my
ладно ой
god 33 I'm ok I'm 43 almost the same
господи 33 мне ну ладно мне 43 почти
age what are you talking about here
ровесники о чём общаетесь тут
yes in fact about the same thing as you I
да на самом деле о том же о чём и вы я
know who you are watched your videos uh in
знаю кто вы смотрела ваши ролики ээ в
principle in short I understand everything about you
принципе короче всё про вас понимаю так
and what do you understand about me
и что вы про меня понимаете
well the fact that you are a Ukrainian
ну то что вы украинский
blogger broadcasting for Ukraine mother and
блогер вещаете за Украину мать а вы за
what are you broadcasting for
что вещаете
I didn't just come out for anything that's just how do you
я ни за что просто вышли
feel about the fact that there is a
вот просто так как относитесь к тому что
war
идёт война
war is always bad you can't have a
война - это всегда плохо к войне нельзя
good attitude towards war
хорошо относиться
who because people are dying who is to blame for the fact that
кто потому что умирают люди кто виноват
Russia attacked Ukraine
в том что Россия напала на Украину
you
вы
know mostly Ukraine but in
знаете в большей степени Украина но
general
вообще
this is diplomacy of two countries if I understood that way they
это дипломатии двух стран если так понял
could have agreed well my opinion is that
могли договориться ну моё мнение такое
you  there with a colleague sit show another
вы там с коллегой сидите покажите ещё
colleague I'll say hello to her colleague
коллегу я поприветствуюсь с ней
colleague chat I'm going to
коллега коллега пообщайся я сейчас буду
download now hello don't return
качать здравствуйте не возвращайте
colleague not cool you're prettier
коллега не прикольный вы красивее
yes I understand got it in short let's
да поняюсь понял короче давайте
chat I just saw your videos
пообщаемся я просто видела ваши ролики
how you make fun of Russians that's
как вы там стебётесь над русскими вот
all
это всё
and I
а
get moral satisfaction no you
получаю моральное удовлетворение нет
know I have one question for you I
знаете у меня к вам такой один вопрос я
know that you most likely won't answer it honestly
знаю что вы скорее всего честно не
why stir up hatred when it already exists
зачем разжигать ненависть когда её и так
uh
ээ
Yes the thing is that look at this on the
Да дело в том что смотрите это по
principle of how for example a Ukrainian
принципу как вот например украинский
drone flies into an oil depot and
беспилотник прилетает в нефтебазу и её
couldn't put it out they can't put it out then they
потушить не мог потушить не могут то
help so that it burns out yes burns out
помогают чтобы оно выгорело да выгорело
and when it burns out it's no longer burning that's why
и когда выгорело уже не горит поэтому
here I help to stir up hatred
так и тут я помогаю разгореть ненависть
so that it burns out and Russia is not
чтобы она уже выгорела и России не
left well
осталась
you understand that this won't happen
ну вы же понимаете что этого не будет
why are
почему
we all here damn well because Russia is a
все мы сюда блин ну потому что Россия -
big country well how do you
это большая страна ну как вы себе
imagine that what I'll explain I'll explain
представляете что что объяснию объясню
we already had such an example the Soviet
уже у нас был такой пример советский
Union we  we destroyed the Russian empire we
Союз мы развалили Российскую империю мы
destroyed it now we need the Russian
развалили теперь нужно российскую
empire you destroyed it personally you
империю вы развалили лично вы
destroyed it Ukrainians well that's not true that's not
разваливали украинцы да
true I
ну это же не так это же неправда в
mean my father went to rallies
смысле у меня отец на митинги ходил
against the Soviet Union like at my house in
против Советского Союза типа у меня дома
short my mother sewed flags underground in short they
короче мама подпольно флаги шила короче
made banners everything ok no well
транспаранты делали всё
that's okay
о'кей нет ну это ладно
but
но
damn right here if it weren't for the economy not for
блин тут же если бы не экономика не
Yeltsin and Gorbachev well how could we have
Ельцин с Горбачёвым ну как бы могли бы и
preserved and the fact that your mother, for example,
сохранить и то что ваша мама допустим
sewed flags specifically it wouldn't have
шила конкретно флаги оно бы ничего не
changed anything here the most important role was played by the
изменило тут самую главную роль сыграла
economy that the economy of the
это экономика то что экономика
Soviet Union it simply well it
Советского Союза она просто ну она не
couldn't continue to
могла дальше продолжать как бы своё
exist and that's right
существование и то правильно то же самое
we now want to do the same with Europe with the
мы с Европой сейчас хотим сделать с
Russian Federation the economy doesn't
Российской Федерацией экономика её не
see it but wait okay okay
видит а подождите хорошо ладно про
everything is clear about Europe about Macron and other
Европу всё понятно про Макрона и прочих
not very smart people and what do you think about Trump
не очень умных людей а как к Трампу
yes Trump is now playing completely to the
да Трамп сейчас играет полностью под
tune of the Russian Federation completely
дудку Российской Федерации полностью
and why do you think so why
а почему как вы думаете так почему
exactly I know there are many versions
именно знаю есть есть многие версии
someone says that he is a KGB agent there
кто-то говорит что он там агент КГБ
someone says that he just wants it
кто-то говорит что он просто хочет так
against China and Europe to set
против Китая и Европы чтобы натравить
Russia against Europe to make a war in Europe
Россию на Европу сделать войну в Европе
shorter and I'm not interested but as an option
короче и меня не интересу а как вариант
and sorry for
а извините что
interrupting no look I'm not interested in the
перебиваю нет смотри меня не интересуют
versions I'm interested in what he's doing what
версии меня интересует что он делает то
he's doing now it's harming Ukraine
что он делает сейчас это вредит Украине
and bringing grist to Russia's mill maybe
и льёт воду на мельницу России возможно
it will change in a month yes but right
она поменяется через месяц да но вот
now it's like that and
сейчас так
as an option if he just doesn't
так а как вариант если он просто не
want that for the US in principle if you
хочет что для США в принципе если
look at it globally the
глобально посмотреть не очень выгоден
Union of Russia and China is not very beneficial and if he just
Союз России и Китая и если он просто
wants well not to entice Russia it's
хочет ну не то чтобы переманить Россию
clear that the US will never be a
понятное дело что США никогда не будет
friend of Russia well globally it will always
другом России ну глобально это всегда
be well not that an enemy but
всё равно будет ну не то чтобы враг но у
it will always have its own interests the interests of the
него всегда будут свои интересы интересы
US and as if it is not beneficial for the US for
США и как бы для США невыгодно чтобы
China and Russia to really
Китай и Россия действительно прямо
become really close well really friends well it's
плотно стали ну прямо друзьями ну
not beneficial for them that's good but why then why should the
невыгодно им это хорошо а зачем зачем
US quarrel with Canada with Europe
США тогда ссорится с Канадой с Европой
oh well I don't know it just seems to me that
ой ну не знаю это просто мне кажется
Trump has some kind of personal ambitions well
личные какие-то амбиции у Трампа ну
like I don't know
типа не знаю
honestly I don't know
честно не знаю
but in any case what is happening now And
но в любом случае то что сейчас это А
by the way have you heard what's going on in Kursk
что кстати в Курске происходит не
there  what what from the boiler room here I hear
слышали там что что с котки вот я слышу
boilers boilers in short they were shouting that the
котлы котлы короче вот кричали что
Russians went through the gas pipe there 100
русские прошли по газовой трубе там 100
people super operation I'm reading
человек супероперация вот уже читаю
right now yes here your Russian
прямо сейчас да вот ваши российские
bloggers are writing that damn all these who
блогеры пишут что блин вот эти все кто
threw in about the victory in short and so
вкидывал про победоньку короче и так
on there well
дальше там да
who is Russia Russia yes oh well
ну кто россия россия да
damn well globally anyway well it wo
ай ну блин ну глобально всё равно же ну
n't fall apart Russia won't fall apart and well
не развалится Россия не развалится и ну
because it's still globally a
потому что это всё равно э глобально
strong power no matter how much you don't
сильная держава как бы вы
want it right look I'll explain the
не не хотели правильно смотри объясню
Soviet Union was even stronger look it will become like this
советский Союз был ещё сильнее смотри
now the
сделается таким образом сейчас
economy of the Russian
разваливается экономика Российской
Federation is falling apart now Putin will put in an analogue of
Федерации сейчас Путинт поставят аналога
Gorbachev yes who will do something like
Горбачёва да который сделает типа аля
perestroika and the collapse of the Russian
перестроечку да и развал российского
state will make a new Yeltsin
государства сделают нового Ельцина
you will promote some kind of Shayga
продвинут у вас да какой-то шайгу
for example and that's it and they will sign and say
например и всё и они подпишут да скажут
that they will dump everything on Putin that it was he who
что вот на Путина всё скинут что это он
like destroyed the country and that's it and what are the
типа развалил страну и всё и какие
downsides
минусы
you
ты же
know Europeans English Anglo-Saxons
знаешь европейцы англичане англосаксы
they know how to do it they know how to do it beautifully  to
они умеют это делать они умеют красиво
destroy the Russian Federation with someone else's hands
чужими руками разваливать Российскую
okay that's all clear I don't think that's how it will
ладно это всё понятно не думаю что так
be but okay
будет но о'кей
let's say I have only one question
предположим у меня только один вопрос
for you globally uh why couldn't
вот глобально к вам э а почему нельзя
everything be resolved peacefully points of view well
было мирно всё решить точки зрения ну
it's clear that in your eyes Russia there in
понятно что в ваших глазах Россия там в
2014 was so aggressive so
четырнадцатом году такой агрес такая вся
bad well well well well well well but be that as it may
плохая вот вот вот вот вот вот но как бы
if we well generally dig yeah yeah
то ни было если мы ну обще копнём да угу
but we were still pretty
а мы всё равно же были довольно
friendly countries there before
дружественными странами там до
2014 before Crimea before
четырнадцатого года до до Крыма до всей
this whole situation with Crimea we still
этой ситуации с Крымом всё равно мы
communicated normally and roughly speaking why was
нормально общались и грубо говоря почему
n't it possible and to your leadership together
нельзя было а вашему руководству вместе
with our I have nothing to do with it I'm not saying that it's
с нашим Я не причём не говорю что прямо
absolutely true I understand I understand look uh
абсолютно я понял понял смотри э
really why wasn't it possible peacefully you
действительно почему нельзя было миром
have to ask your leadership
это надо спросить ваше руководство
because you attacked us not we were
потому что вы же на нас напали не мы
doing something and we attacked you you attacked
что-то нелись и мы на вас напали вы
us took Crimea Donetsk
напали на нас забрали у нас Крым Донецк
Lugansk from us then went even further yes you
Луганск потом ещё дальше пошли да вы
attacked us we were generally against war
напали мы мы вообще против войны были
it was you who attacked us well
это вы напали на нас
because again  there are zones of
ну так потому что опять же есть зоны
influence from which you wanted to leave, roughly
влияния из которых вы хотели уйти грубо
speaking, you wanted to go to Europe, that's
говоря вы захотели там в Европу вот это
all stop stop stop what does it mean there are
вот всё стоп стоп стоп что значит есть
zones of influence from which you wanted to leave
зоны влияния из которых вы захотели уйти
we are a free state where we want to
мы свободное государство куда хотим туда
go there and what's the problem
и входим в чём проблема
globally the problem is that a free
глобально проблема в том что свободное
state okay but these are all
государство о'кей но это же все
conventions in that sense look and in that
условности в том плане смотрите а в том
sense that let's say look well globally
плане что допустим смотрите ну глобально
Russia would want its own or not Russia
Россия захотела бы своё или не Россия
someone else I don't know any other
кто-нибудь ещё не знаю любое другое
state would want its influence on
государство захотело бы своё влияние на
some Cuba Mexico and now the USA would be
какую-нибудь Кубу Мексику а сейчас США
against that's right again well what do you
же был бы против правильно ещё раз ну
mean against well
что значит против
it would start to resist it well so
ну оно оно бы стало этому противиться ну
what would it become the same well maybe
и что оно бы стало то же самое ну может
not a special operation something else well
быть не спецоперацию что-нибудь другое
because that's how the world works that well
ну потому что так устроен мир что ну
look this is the law of the strong which
смотрите вот это право сильного которое
you don't recognize but it exists there's nothing like that
вы так не признаёте но оно есть ничего
nowhere that is I'm right
такого нет никуда то есть я правильно
damn about don't disappear don't
блин про не пропадай не
disappear you've obviously got a call come on turn
пропадай тебе звонок видно пошёл давай
on I'll wait
включись я дождусь
damn hello
блин здравствуйте
hello you're 18 yes yes you
здравствуйте вам 18 лет есть да очень
look very young thank you but I'm 18 and
молодо выглядите спасибо но мне и 18 и
yes well super what about  you talk about
есть ну супер о чём общаетесь
what you talk about
о чём общаетесь
yes about everything I understand I am from the city of Khmelnitsky
да обо всём понял я из города Хмельницки
and where are you from Moscow I understand a native who
а вы откуда из Москвы понял кореная
came here yes yes a native yes a native yes who are you studying to be I am
понаехавши да да кореная да кореная да
studying I am in the eleventh
на кого учитесь я учусь я в одиннадцатом
grade I understand well 18 is somehow yes I understood yes yes
классе понял ну 18 есть както да понял
super super
да да супер супер
what question do you want to ask a person from Ukraine well how do you
какой хотите вопрос человеку из Украины
feel about Russian
ну как вы относитесь вообще к русским
people in general Russians are normal for example
людям крусским нормально вот например
Russians who live in Ukraine are fighting
русские которые живут в Украине воюют
against the Russian Federation well that
против Российской Федерации
is yes yes that is for example and Russians who live
ну это да да то есть например а русские
in Russia I have a bad attitude towards them they are fighting
украинцам которые живут в России воюют
against Ukraine Ukrainians who live in Russia are fighting against Ukraine I have a bad attitude towards Czechs
против Украины плохо отношусь чещенцам
who live in Russia and are fighting against
которые живут в России и воюют против
Ukraine pass that is it is very simple here
Украины прохо то есть тут очень просто к
I have a
гражданам Российской Федерации я
bad attitude towards citizens of the Russian Federation regardless of their
отношусь плохо независимо от их
nationality I have a good attitude towards citizens of Ukraine regardless of their nationality well that is
национальностей к гражданам Украине я
strange because well for
ну это странно потому что ну вот
example in fact you also have a bad
например по факту ко мне вы тоже плохо
attitude towards me you treat me
относитесь относитесь
but I do nothing well like you well that is
да я же ничего не делаю ну как вы
because in  that's what we
вот Да вот потому что в том-то и
treat you as you do nothing and what about
относимся что вы ничего не делаете а что
us as we what can we do we
мы как мы что мы можем сделать мы
understand that you can't do anything
понимаем что вы ничего не можете сделать
yes but we can't because you ca
да но мы не можем из-за того что вы
n't do anything we can't
ничего не можете сделать мы не можем к
start to treat you well no not
вам начать хорошо относиться нет не
well just neutrally like not well not good it does
хорошо просто нейтрально типа не хорошо
n't work out look well I
неплохо не получается вот смотрите ну я
can't force myself to
не могу заставить себя нейтрально
treat you neutrally I can't here what
относиться к вам я не могу вот что я
can I do to
могу сделать чтобы нейстрально
treat you neutrally that is you don't look at me with
относиться к вам то есть вы на меня
direct hatred yes you don't have direct hatred
смотрите не прямо ненависть да у вас не
but such a slight contempt
не прямо ненависть но такое презрение
there is well I treat
лёгкое есть ну я отношусь нейтрально к
Ukrainians neutrally these are also people like people are
украинцам это тоже люди типа люди
divided into good and bad like whose
делятся на хорошие и плохие типа а чей
Crimea is by the way what do you think Crimea is Russia you
Крым кстати как вы считаете крым России
see and so let's do it as you
вот видите и вот давайте так как вы
think what you say Crimea is Russia will
считаете то что вы говорите Крым России
help me treat you neutrally
поможет мне нейтрально отнестись к вам
or will I still look at you as
или всё-таки буду смотреть на вас как на
Sorry I don't know this is your opinion well so what do
Извините я не знаю это ваше мнение ну
you think here you are telling me a person
вот как вы думаете вот вы мне человеку
from Ukraine that Russia
из Украины говорите вот то что Россия
occupied Crimea - is it normal that
оккупировала Крым - это нормально что
Crimea is Russia yes what do you think I
Крым - это Россия да как вы думаете я
will look at you as or how  I
буду смотреть на вас на или как на
think of a normal person, I think of a
нормального человека думаю на
normal person,
нормального
so it's obvious that my view is not entirely clear, yes,
так видно мой взгляд не совсем ясен
I understand that you treat me with contempt, well, it's just that Well, yes, well, it's
да я понимаю что вы с презрением ко мне
just that why don't
Ну да ну просто почему вот у людей
Russian people have this with Ukrainians, I don't
русских нет такого к украинцам не знаю
know, I don't know either, well, somehow I
не знаю я вот тоже не знаю ну как-то я
asked myself this question, I even went to a
задавал себе этот вопрос я ходил даже к
psychologist because at first I thought:
психологу потому что я сначала думал:
"Well, why do I look at people who
"Ну почему я смотрю на людей которые
say that Crimea is Russia, how?"  And they
говорят что Крым - это Россия как?" И
advised me: "See a psychologist"
мне посоветовали: "Обратись к психологу"
because it's not normal, why do
потому что это ненормально ну почему
people just think like that, well, it's not their
люди просто так считают ну они же не
fault, they're not doing anything, so I went, well,
виноваты они ничего не делают я пошёл ну
everyone has their own opinion, yes, I went to a
вот у всех мнение своё да да я пошёл к
psychologist and said: "Look, I
психологу и говорю: "Смотрите у меня вот
have this internal problem that I
есть ну такая внутренняя проблема что я
can't come to terms with other people's opinions," for
не могу смириться с чужими мнениями" да
example, if a person says that
вот например если человек говорит что
Crimea is Russia, yes, I start to
Крым - это Россия да я начинаю резко на
look at it sharply as if it were, yes, so I say:
неё смотреть как на да вот и говорю:
"Advise me how I can, uh, work through this,
"Посоветуйте как может ээ проработать да
what psychological techniques are there to work through this,
какие есть техники психологические
" well, yes, they
проработать вот это" ну да мне мне
prescribed me certain psychological
назначили определённые психологические
practices, and they said: "Go to
практики ну и сказали: "Эходи в
chatroulette," yes, that is, there is such a thing as
чатрулетку" да то есть есть такая
chatroulette therapy, we have a very
чатрулеттерапия у нас есть очень
famous psychologist named Andrey
известный психолог называется Андрей
Popyk, yes, he developed a very good one
Попык да он разработал очень хорошую
called chatroulette therapy, yes, that
называется четрулеточную терапию да то
is, if you,
есть если ты
for example, too, well, somehow think that
например слишком ну как-то считаешь что
you're looking in vain at people who think
ты зря смотришь на людей которые считают
that Crimea is Russia, then go to
что Крым-Россия как на то заходи в
chatroulette and you'll be there for a day or three
чат-рулетку и ты там побудешь день-три
weeks, depending on the degree of your
недели в зависимости от степени твоей
neglect and you will understand that it is in
запущенности и поймёшь что это в
principle normal to consider people who
принципе нормально считать людей которые
think that Crimea is Russia
считают что Крым-Россия
well excuse me just well well
ну извините просто
how can I say that I am from Russia
ну ну как сказать то что я из России
of course I will think so well that Yes well and
конечно я буду так считать ну это Да ну
I am from Ukraine of course I will consider
а я я из Украины я конечно буду считать
you yes well I understand that yes I understand well so what well that is it is
вас да ну это я понимаю да я понимаю ну
symmetrical
так а что ну то есть это же симметрично
you think that Crimea is Russia yes it is your
вы считаете что Крым Россия да это ваше
right to think yes and I think I
право считать да а у меня я вот считаю
look at you as I also
смотрю на вас как на Это же у меня тоже
have the right to look at things like that well yes but
есть право смотреть на вещи так ну да но
I am offended well how offended well you know
мне обидно ну как обидно ну такое знаете
life is unfair yes
жизнь несправедлива да
and what do you think you need to do so that
а как вы думаете что вам нужно сделать
I do not look at you as a piece
чтобы я не смотрел на вас как на кусок
personally I can do nothing well how
лично я ничего не могу сделать
can you for example tell me something
ну как вы например мне можете что-то
so that I somehow change
сказать чтобы я как-то изменил
tried my opinion of you as a piece
попробовал своё мнение о вас как о куске
[music]
[музыка]
well look firstly people
ну смотрите во-первых у у людей у
each person has their own opinion and secondly you
каждого человека своё мнение а во-вторых
can't think that I am Russian and you can't
нельзя то что вот я русская и нельзя
consider that I as a person am not I do
считать то что я же как человек не Я же
n't know at all whether you are Russian or
вообще не знаю русская вы или там
Ukrainian or German in general whose are
украинская или там немецкая вообще чья
you like you are saying that Crimea is
вы типа вы говорите что Крым - это
Russia well well  because I'm from Russia
Россия ну ну потому что я из России
so I'll keep thinking stop that
поэтому я так и буду считать стоп то
is it turns out you support uh the
есть получается вы поддерживаете ээ
seizure of territories of other states and the
захват территорий других государств и
killing of people in another country interesting
убийство людей в другой стране интересно
and just because you're from Russia yes yes
и просто потому что вы из России да да
cool but when uh a girl
прикольно а вот когда э-э девочка
who lived in Nazi Germany she
которая жила в гитлеровской Германии она
supported the attack on other countries
поддерживала нападение на другие страны
just because she lived in
просто из-за того что она жила в
Germany
Германии
remember everything yes if you have
всё так запомните да якщо у вас виникає
some kind of thought that this is wrong that you are
якась думка що це неправильно що ви
surprised at someone who respects Crimea Russia
дивитесь на тих хто вважае Крим России
like Yes
як Да викону техніку психолога Андрія
I've reached out to the technique of psychologist Andriy Popik he's a really
Попика я до ньго звернувся реально
cool guy and he says: "Go to
крутий чувак да він каже: "Заходь в
roulette and in a day you will no longer
рулетку да и одт дня и ти вже не будеш
think about what you have some kind of healing you
думати що це у тебе якесь відхилення ти
will really be surprised at them like and
будеш реально дивитись на них як на и
understand that this is normal  nature state do
розуміти що це нормальний природй стан
not persuade yourself to
тому не вдмовляйте собі в тому щоб
watch them as if you
дивитись на них як на
liked psychological
отак кому сподобалась психологична
training psychological training from Father Andrey you
тренин психотрен від Оця Андроя вы
know what to
знаете что
do subscribe to Telegram right
робити підпишись на й Telegram прям
now here it is and
зараз ось він а
priest it is very and very important youtube
попик це дуже і дуже важливо youtube
drives us through carts into a shadow
заганяе нас чере каргеорки в тіньовий
ban and very many videos are not shown to
бан і дуже багато відео не показуется
people at times information
людям вчасно не показуется інформація
about streams is not shown so that we have a
про стрими тому для того щоб ми мали
quick connection subscribe right
оперативний зв'язок підпишиться прям
now and priest there in telegram okmde
зараз а попик там в телеграмі окмде ще
also interesting and useful information and we are
теж цікава и корисна інформація і ми
obliged to protect you  constant
повинні з вами тримати постійний
operational connection independently from that will
оперативный зв'язок незалежно від того
show you about this YouTube glory of
чи покаже вам про цей YouTube слава
Ukraine subscribe
Україні підпишись